<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Brian Rahadi</title>
    <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brian Rahadi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 14:54:10 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brianrahadi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 10:20:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianrahadi.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>One of the reasons why I chose computer science is how easy it is to build projects with minimal tools (just a laptop!). Therefore, I have listed some projects which I thought to be the most interesting ordered from the top.
Parkland A full-stack amusement park website that have many features. It allows user login, signup, and it has its own reviews page with full CRUD functionality. User can make their own cards as an entry ticket and add the balance using Stripe API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Langara CS to SFU CS/ SoSy Transfer Guide</title>
      <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/sfu-cs-transfer-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 14:54:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/sfu-cs-transfer-guide/</guid>
      <description>Last Updated: 28 June 2022
Introduction Hello! My name is Brian. I have just transferred to Simon Fraser University&amp;rsquo;s Software Systems program this summer after graduating from Langara with an Associate in Computer Science.
In this guide, I will show you all the knowledge that I have accumulated to successfully transfer to Simon Fraser University (CS/ SoSy). You can also check out this guide for the UBC version.
My guide here is mainly intended for Langara College students aiming to transfer to SFU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why you should write more ✍(◔◡◔)</title>
      <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/whywrite/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 20:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/whywrite/</guid>
      <description>In my transition period from junior high to high school years, I used to be paid to write. Sounds cool at first, until I told everyone that I am just writing for a game guide.
Looking back, I regret that I did not write as much again. Aside from the good money that I got from writing the blog posts, I got to know more about the game mechanics. Writing has helped me to refine my understanding of the game, allowing me to become a better player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Summary - The Subtle Art of Not Giving a Fuck</title>
      <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/subtleart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:39:31 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/subtleart/</guid>
      <description>Self-help advice which tells you to become the person you want to be only reinforces the idea that you are not that thing Pursuing something only reinforces that you lack it in the first place. Everyone wants you to believe that the secret to a good life is to have a nicer job or a better car or a prettier girlfriend. The key to a good life is not giving a fuck about more; it’s giving a fuck about less, giving a fuck about only what is true and immediate and important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Summary - The Almanack of Naval Ravikant</title>
      <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/navalmanack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:31:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/navalmanack/</guid>
      <description>Building Wealth Understand How Wealth Is Created It’s not really about hard work. You can work in a restaurant eighty hours a week, and you’re not going to get rich. Getting rich is about knowing what to do, who to do it with, and when to do it. It is much more about understanding than purely hard work.
Wealth is the thing you want. Wealth is assets that earn while you sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Summary - Deep Work</title>
      <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/deepwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:20:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/deepwork/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The ability to perform deep work is becoming increasingly rare at exactly the same time it is becoming increasingly valuable in our economy.&amp;rdquo;
 What is Deep Work? “Professional activity performed in a state of distraction-free concentration that push your cognitive capabilities to their limit. These efforts create new value, improve your skill, and are hard to replicate.”
Types of Deep Work
 Monastic → Full deep work, Bimodal → Seasonal deep Work, Journalistic → Anytime deep work The Rhythmic Philosophy of Deep Work Scheduling → The easiest way to consistently start deep work sessions is to make it a habit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Summary - 7 Habits of Highly Effective Teens</title>
      <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/7habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:15:28 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/7habits/</guid>
      <description>We need a paradigm, paradigm is the way you see something, your point of view. Paradigms need to be principle-centered
   Be Proactive
 Proactive is the opposite of reactive. They are the one who have the control over your attitude. They make choices based on values. They think before they act. They recognize that they can’t control everything that happens to them, but they can control what they do about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Summary - How to Become a Straight-A Student</title>
      <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/straighta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 10:06:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/straighta/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The simple truth is that the brute force techniques used by most students are incredibly inefficient.&amp;rdquo; - Cal Newport
   Study in focused, but short blocks rather than pseudo-working through the night.
 Find your ideal study length. (50 minutes with 10 minutes rests, 30-5) Manage the time in daily calendar that can be updated so you can strictly follow it.    Find your most common excuses with a work progress journal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Summary - Atomic Habits</title>
      <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/atomichabits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 09:33:41 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianrahadi.github.io/posts/atomichabits/</guid>
      <description>”We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence is not an act, but a habit.” - Aristotle
 “The costs of your good habits are in the present. The costs of your bad habits are in the future.”
 Habits = Freedom: “Habits do not restrict freedom. They create it. In fact, the people who don’t have their habits handled are often the ones with the least amount of freedom.” Systems &amp;gt; Goals: “My results had very little to do with the goals I set and nearly everything to do with the systems I followed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://brianrahadi.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 21:03:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianrahadi.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Intro My name is Brian Rahadi. I&amp;rsquo;m currently studying Software Systems (subset of CS) at Simon Fraser University.
During my time here, I realized how beautiful life is. This website will be my main place to dump ideas and share it into the world.
Since my freshman year of college, I have developed a keen interest of computer software. There will be many more things that I have not yet to figure out :).</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
